A Guide to the Papers of Ann Beattie
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of Ann Beattie 1986-1990
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
10414-v
This collection consists of 35 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was deposited 1991 July 19
Scope and Content Information
The collection contains typescripts of short stories by Beattie, an interview with her by Patrick H. Samway, and uncorrected page proofs of advance copies of books sent to her for review with accompanying correspondence.
Contents List
- Manuscripts and Related Material Re Ann Beattie
  - "Home to Marie" by Ann Beattie in The New Yorker1986, TMs (Box 1)
  - "Horatio's Trick" by Ann Beattie in The New Yorker1987, 3 TMs (Box 1)
  - Interview with Ann Beattie by Patrick H. Samway, published in America1990 (Box 1)
  - Letters from Editors to Ann Beattie re advance copies of books sent to her for review 1989-1990 (Box 1)
  - "The Longest Day of the Year" by Ann Beattie n.d., TMs (Box 1)
  - "Name Day" by Ann Beattie (previously titled "Sherando") ca. 1989, TMs (Box 1)
  - "Name Day" by Ann Beattie 1989, Page Proofs (Box 1)
  - "Such Occasions" by Ann Beattie n.d., TMsS (Box 1)
  - "The Sweetest Songs" by Ann Beattie in ca. 1990, TMs & Printed (Box 1)
  - "What Was Mine" by Ann Beattie in n.d., TMsS (Box 1)
  - n.d., TMs (Box 1)
  - "Windy Day at the Reservoir" by Ann Beattie 1989, TMs (Box 1)
  - "You Know What" by Ann Beattie n.d., TMs & TMsS (Box 1)
  - Untitled Short Story by Ann Beattie n.d., TMs (Box 1)
- Manuscripts & Advance Proofs by Other Authors
  - My Father's Geisha by James Gordon Bennett 1990 (Box 2)
  - The Revolution of Little Girls by Blanche McCrary Boyd 1991 (Box 2)
  - Sexual Intercourse by Rose Boyt 1989 (Box 2)
  - Boomtown by David Breskin 1989 (Box 2)
  - Biodegradeable Soap by Amy Ephron 1991 (Box 2)
  - Swallow Hard by Sarah Gaddis 1990 (Box 2)
  - Family Fictions by Richard Hall 1991 (Box 2)
  - Spense & Lila by Bobbie Ann Mason 1988 (Box 2)
  - The Last Airmen by Roger Rawlings 1989 (Box 2)
  - If Not On Earth, Then In Heaven by Joel Redon n.d., 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Bones by Joyce Thompson 1991 (Box 2)
  - My Life With Darwin by Molly Best Tinsley 1991 (Box 2)